Heorhii Huziuk

NodeJS Engineer

+48451586161 | huziukwork@gmail.com | linkedin | github | telegram

Professional Experience:

2024 - now FarmFusion

Technologies: PostgreSQL, Typeorm, NodeJS(Express + TypeScript), ELK, Docker **Key Contributions:**

- Managed interactions with frontend and hardware parts.
- Supervised the work of front and backend developers.
- Participated in the development of the application architecture.
- Performed DevOps tasks: database setup, application deployment, containerization,
 CI/CD, set ELK stack to aggregate logs
- Conducted unit-testing with Postman.

2024 - now Livesey

GitHub: livesey-finance

Technologies: PostgreSQL, MySQL, NodeJS(all-agnostic + JavaScript), Redis/KeyDB, Docker, ELK **Key Contributions:**

- Designed and implemented the *all-agnostic* principle
- Worked with async API(Async queues/async pools)
- Designed and implemented the DDD architecture in main module
- Wrote frontend using Vue
- Published reusable modules on NPM, contributing to the open-source community and enabling code reusability across projects.
- Created custom modules for working with databases, HTTP, data parsing, validation, etc.

2022 - 2024 Freelance

Technologies: PostgreSQL, Typeorm, NodeJS(Express), Redis, Docker **Key Contributions:**

- Utilized MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL databases to store user data.
- Conducted unit testing with Jest and documentation with Swagger.
- Deployed project on Google Cloud Platform.
- Implemented Domain-Driven Design (DDD) architecture.
- Designed of application architectures that met the principle of SOLID, GRASP

Skills:

- Programming Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, SQL, GraphQL, C/C++
- Frameworks/Platforms: Node.js (Express)
- Databases: PostgreSQL, MySQL, Redis/KeyDB, MongoDB
- ORMs/ODMs: TypeORM, Sequelize, Mongoose
- DevOps: Docker, Docker-Compose, Google Cloud Platform
- Operating Systems: Linux (Ubuntu, Kali), MacOS
- Other Tools: Swagger, Jest, WebSockets, MQTT protocol, Git, XML, JSON, ELK
- Principles and Patterns: SOLID, MVC, OOP, DDD, REST, CI/CD, GoF patterns, GRASP
- Soft skills: Creativity, Attention to Detail, Critical Thinking, Problem-Solving, Fast Learner, Leadership

Education:

2018 - 2022
 2022 - Present
 West Pomeranian University of Technology: Computer Science/Information Systems Engineering

Languages:

English (B2), Polish (B2), German (Goethe-Zertifikat B2), Ukrainian (Native), Russian (Native)

About me:

I'm a developer with experience in implementing complex projects using native all-agnostic NodeJS and other related technologies like ORMs and frameworks. My interests include open-source contributing, solving problems using complex async technologies in JS, cloud technologies, reading technical and scientific books related to computer science and economics, cycling, outdoor activities and working with electronics and hardware.